<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Genesys CX as Code Workshop on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</title>
    <link>https://genesys-samples.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Genesys CX as Code Workshop on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://genesys-samples.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CX As Code</title>
      <link>https://genesys-samples.github.io/020-cx-as-code-and-terraform/10_first.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://genesys-samples.github.io/020-cx-as-code-and-terraform/10_first.html</guid>
      <description>What is CX as Code? CX as Code is a configuration tool that allows you to define Genesys Cloud objects such as Queues, Skills, Users, etc. in plain text files and then apply that configuration across a single or multiple Genesys Cloud CX organizations
 CX as Code Resources CX as Code resources are used to create configuration components using inputs (such as the name of a skill), however; some resources have numerous dependencies, or configuration objects that must exist or be created in tandem for the resource to be created</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gitting Started... haha</title>
      <link>https://genesys-samples.github.io/030-using-cx-as-code/10_gitting-started-haha.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://genesys-samples.github.io/030-using-cx-as-code/10_gitting-started-haha.html</guid>
      <description>Create a local file repository This is fancy talk for creating a folder locally on your machine that will be used to store code and development projects
 It is best practice to not include spaces in the name of this folder, or files in general while developing
 Open this folder within VSCode You can either right click within this folder and select “Open with code” or navigate to it from VSCode Directly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Your Code Base</title>
      <link>https://genesys-samples.github.io/030-using-cx-as-code/20_buidlingyourcodebase.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://genesys-samples.github.io/030-using-cx-as-code/20_buidlingyourcodebase.html</guid>
      <description>Setting up your file structure Create two files in VS code:
 Variables.tf Main.tf  Copy the code snippit below and paste it into your Variables.tf file. Once copied over you will need to enter your Oauth client ID and secret with the information from the Oauth client you created in the previous step. You will also need to replace the AWS Region (found in the AWS region name column in the linked article) with the AWS region your Genesys Cloud org resides in</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraform</title>
      <link>https://genesys-samples.github.io/020-cx-as-code-and-terraform/20_second.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://genesys-samples.github.io/020-cx-as-code-and-terraform/20_second.html</guid>
      <description>What is Terraform Terraform is a tool for building and managing infrastructures. It takes in configuration files, which specify how the resources should be set up and configured. Terraform will generate an execution plan describing what needs to be done to reach the desired state. Terraform then applies the plan and builds the specified infrastructure. When new changes are made to the configuration files, Terraform is able to detect differences and generate incremental execution plans for changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Cases</title>
      <link>https://genesys-samples.github.io/020-cx-as-code-and-terraform/30_third.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://genesys-samples.github.io/020-cx-as-code-and-terraform/30_third.html</guid>
      <description>Why use CX as Code? You may be looking at some of the resource articles, or have skipped ahead a few pages in the workshop and asked yourself &amp;ldquo;Why would I go through all of this to simply construct a skill?&amp;rdquo;
While this workshop is intended to provide a foundational knowledge of CX as Code, the scope of CX as Code is well beyond spending 4 hours building a skill</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
