<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Using CX as Code on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</title>
    <link>https://genesys-samples.github.io/030-using-cx-as-code.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Using CX as Code on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://genesys-samples.github.io/030-using-cx-as-code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gitting Started .. Git it?</title>
      <link>https://genesys-samples.github.io/030-using-cx-as-code/10_gitting-started-haha.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://genesys-samples.github.io/030-using-cx-as-code/10_gitting-started-haha.html</guid>
      <description>Create a local file repository First Things first, we will be creating a local file repository or &amp;ldquo;repo&amp;rdquo;. This is fancy talk for creating a folder locally on your machine that will be used to store code and development projects. Storing code on your machine allows you to work on and make changes to your project before pushing your changes to a GitHub repository where the pipeline configuration resides.
 It is best practice to not include spaces in the name of this folder, or files in general while developing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Your Code Base</title>
      <link>https://genesys-samples.github.io/030-using-cx-as-code/20_buidlingyourcodebase.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://genesys-samples.github.io/030-using-cx-as-code/20_buidlingyourcodebase.html</guid>
      <description>Setting up your file structure From here, we will be starting from scratch with two terraform scripts and how to get started with terraform. Below you will see two seperate terraform files you will beed to create. Within VS Code, create new folders with the naming convention below:
Create two files in VS code:
 Variables.tf Main.tf  Copy the code snippit below and paste it into your Variables.tf file. Once copied over you will need to enter your Oauth client ID and secret with the information from the Oauth client you created in the previous step.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
